[{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980360851,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":16191,"timeElapsed":107373},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980372215,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":11359,"timeElapsed":118737},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980396909,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":24689,"timeElapsed":143431},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980417301,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":20388,"timeElapsed":163824},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980435034,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":17728,"timeElapsed":181556},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980471919,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":36882,"timeElapsed":218442},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980481020,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":9097,"timeElapsed":227543},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980493752,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":12727,"timeElapsed":240274},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980497815,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"227","question":"Do you have any unusual genetic traits (for example, cilantro tasting like soap, or particular allergies)?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":4059,"timeElapsed":244338},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980510697,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":11007,"timeElapsed":257220},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980518808,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":8109,"timeElapsed":265331},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980525357,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":6548,"timeElapsed":271880},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980634100,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":108741,"timeElapsed":380623},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980639498,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":5395,"timeElapsed":386021},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980652962,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":13461,"timeElapsed":399485},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980657409,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":4444,"timeElapsed":403932},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980669906,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":12493,"timeElapsed":416429},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980675539,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":5630,"timeElapsed":422062},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980698899,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":21574,"timeElapsed":445422},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980703281,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":4381,"timeElapsed":449804},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980708081,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":4799,"timeElapsed":454604},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980735273,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":27188,"timeElapsed":481796},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980760953,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":25678,"timeElapsed":507476},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980772731,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":11775,"timeElapsed":519254},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980789096,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":16361,"timeElapsed":535618},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980797677,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":8578,"timeElapsed":544200},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980802793,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"219","question":"What are some topics you find yourself drawn to (for example, the roman empire, medieval cat paintings) that aren’t related to other aspects of your life?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":5113,"timeElapsed":549316},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980813788,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":9292,"timeElapsed":560311},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980825536,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":11744,"timeElapsed":572059},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980832436,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":6895,"timeElapsed":578958},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980854078,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":21638,"timeElapsed":600601},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980862744,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":8662,"timeElapsed":609267},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980876907,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":14160,"timeElapsed":623430},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980879957,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":3047,"timeElapsed":626480},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980908281,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":28321,"timeElapsed":654804},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980917214,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"7","question":"Do you have a secret hunch about how you will die?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":8928,"timeElapsed":663736},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980933894,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":15044,"timeElapsed":680417},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980944668,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":10770,"timeElapsed":691190},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980951486,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":6814,"timeElapsed":698008},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980959984,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":8495,"timeElapsed":706507},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980977221,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":17234,"timeElapsed":723744},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980980690,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3465,"timeElapsed":727212},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980992334,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":11641,"timeElapsed":738857},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980998138,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":5802,"timeElapsed":744661},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981008701,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":10560,"timeElapsed":755224},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981011182,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"113","question":"Who are the most important people in your life right now? Has this changed over time?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":2477,"timeElapsed":757705},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981028087,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":15579,"timeElapsed":774610},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981044898,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":16808,"timeElapsed":791421},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981053237,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":8337,"timeElapsed":799760},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981063744,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":10505,"timeElapsed":810267},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981066435,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2687,"timeElapsed":812958},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981073565,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":7127,"timeElapsed":820088},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981076318,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2750,"timeElapsed":822841},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981084117,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":7795,"timeElapsed":830640},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981088956,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"3","question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":4836,"timeElapsed":835479},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981094736,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Before making a telephone call, do you ever rehearse what you are going to say? Why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5778,"timeElapsed":841259},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981109435,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":13084,"timeElapsed":855958},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981118718,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":9279,"timeElapsed":865241},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981124627,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":5905,"timeElapsed":871150},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981138487,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":13857,"timeElapsed":885010},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981141356,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":2865,"timeElapsed":887878},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981149625,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":8267,"timeElapsed":896148},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981152121,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":2493,"timeElapsed":898644},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981159029,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":6904,"timeElapsed":905552},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981162090,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3057,"timeElapsed":908613},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981180783,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":17393,"timeElapsed":927306},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981184793,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4007,"timeElapsed":931316},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981190380,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5585,"timeElapsed":936903},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981199641,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":9259,"timeElapsed":946164},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981202321,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2677,"timeElapsed":948844},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981207787,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":5462,"timeElapsed":954310},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981210431,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2641,"timeElapsed":956954},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981222887,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":12453,"timeElapsed":969410},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981225100,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"66","question":"What parts of yourself do you feel you have to hide or tone down in different social situations?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2210,"timeElapsed":971623},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981231475,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5046,"timeElapsed":977998},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981234809,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3330,"timeElapsed":981332},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981240486,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":5674,"timeElapsed":987009},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981253022,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":12532,"timeElapsed":999545},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981255557,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":2533,"timeElapsed":1002080},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981262827,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":7267,"timeElapsed":1009350},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981266059,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":3229,"timeElapsed":1012582},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981271771,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5709,"timeElapsed":1018294},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981275240,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"157","question":"What is your favorite holiday? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3467,"timeElapsed":1021763},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981296792,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":20317,"timeElapsed":1043315},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981301158,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4362,"timeElapsed":1047681},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981304428,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":3267,"timeElapsed":1050951},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981312516,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":8087,"timeElapsed":1059039},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981316583,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":4065,"timeElapsed":1063105},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981321360,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":4776,"timeElapsed":1067883},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981323799,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":2435,"timeElapsed":1070322},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981330303,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":6501,"timeElapsed":1076826},{"subjectID":"l2erz2nj4s","prolificID":"664212577c09653c94741aab","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25c48bd309aee9007e5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981333547,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"190","question":"Pick a feeling you’ve experienced before for which there isn’t currently a word in English. Describe the feeling and make up a word for it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":3242,"timeElapsed":1080070}]